Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is peanut butter halfbaked. Let me
show you how to make it. We're starting
this off with a peanut butter base. So,
use your favorite high protein milk,
some peanut butter powder, real peanut
butter, sweetener, salt, zantham gum,
and then blend that all together with an
immersion blender. The immersion blender
is a recent change for me, but honestly,
it helps so much, especially on recipes
like these that use peanut butter or
cream cheese or a lot of powders. So,
once that initial spin is done, it
should come out pretty close to being
done. You can tell if the sides start to
melt down a little bit. If that's the
case, then start scraping down the sides
and then hollow out a hole in the middle
for our mixins that I just popped up on
screen. These are two of my favorite
protein snacks and two of the three
companies I actually have a code with.
Code FPF will save you some money at
checkout on both of these sites. Highly
recommend trying these out. These are
some of my favorite Ninja Creamy
mix-ins. Also, pro tip for these, chop
these into your desired size, freeze
them, and then mix them